ANDRE ALLEN

Lead Cybersecurity Analyst - Web Application

drellenster@gmail.com • Kingston, Jamaica

Detail oriented professional with a passion for technology and several years experience in the field of cybersecurity. Willing to put my soft skills and technical skills to use in the aim of helping your company achieve its goals.

Experience

Lead Cyber Analyst: Web Application Security

SYMPTAI CONSULTING LIMITED, Kingston, JAMAICA

December 2018 - Present

- Performed security awareness training to clients.
- Performed social engineering engagements.
- Performed security testing of APIs, Web apps and Mobile Apps using both manual and automated methods with OWASP Top 10 and PCI-DSS in mind.
- Conducted external black and grey box testing.
- Conducted internal penetration testing.
- Collaborated with developers to conduct code reviews of new features.
- Wrote scripts to prove a concept
- Wrote automated tests
- Provided feedback on user stories during sprint planning and backlog refinement so that the scrum team codes with security in mind.
- Documented findings and solutions in a concise manner so clients can benefit.
- Rated risks based on ease of exploit, likelihood and business impact.
- Reviewed security architecture diagrams.
- Ensured technology being used are in accordance with industry standard.

Information Security Consultant

OPENWAVE INFORMATION SECURITY LTD, Kingston, JAMAICA

March 2017 - December 2018

- Performed security awareness training to clients.
- Performed security testing of APIs, Web apps and Mobile Apps using both manual and automated methods
- Collaborated with developers to conduct code reviews of new features
- Provided feedback on user stories during sprint planning and backlog refinement so that the scrum team codes with security in mind
- Documented findings and solutions in a concise manner so clients can benefit

Developer

CASEWARE, Kingston, JAMAICA

July 2016 - April 2017

Developed features in line with business requirements using Agile methodologies.

- Informed stakeholders of project issues, challenges and status.
- Participated in Scrum Ceremonies
- Conducted Pair Programming

Education

Bachelor Of Science (B.S.) In Computer Science University Of The West Indies Mona, Kingston, Jamaica November 2016

Skills

- Penetration Testing
- Vulnerability Assessment
- Project Management
- Control Recommendations
- Critical Thinking
- Detailed Oriented
- Creative Problems Solving

Certifications

- CEH Certified Ethical Hacker
- EWPT eLearn Web application Penetration Tester
- CSM Certified Scrum Master (ScrumAlliance)

Awards

- Best Undergraduate Demonstration Presentation: First Place The University of the West Indies Mona
- Extraordinary Team Member & Providing Exceptional Results. (Financial Year of 2019 to 2020)

Online Presence

- Blog article posted about OWASP Top 10
- Participated as a speaker at a Tech Symposium
- Active on TryHackMe